<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<people>
	<person>
		<name>Ryan Giggs</name>
		<position>Midfielder</position>
		<country>Wales</country>
		<DOB>29 NOV 1973</DOB>
        <debut>2 MAR 1991</debut>
        <left>3 JUL 2016</left>
        <image>Ryan.jpg</image>
        <details>Ryan Giggs is a famous British-Welsh former footballer who is presently the manager of the national team of Wales. He captained the English schoolboy-level team against Germany and helped them gain an entry into professional football. He became the youngest member of 'Manchester United' and of the Welsh senior team at the age of 17. He established himself as one of English football's best left wingers and played a major role in 'Manchester United' throughout his professional football career. He ultimately became the assistant manager of 'Manchester United' and then c=became the full-time manager of the national team of Wales. Giggs has won several awards and state honours, such as the 'Order of the British Empire' (OBE) and an honarary Masters of Arts degree from Salford University for his contribution to football and charity work. He married Stacey Cooke and had two children. However, he was linked with a lot of women, and this became the reason for his divorce a few years later. Eventually, his relationship with his family was adversely affected. This, however, did not dampen his professional career, and he remains to be a respected sportsperson.</details>
        <website>https://www.manutd.com/en/players-and-staff/detail/ryan-giggs</website>
     </person>
    <person>
        <name>Bobby Charlton</name>
        <position>Forward</position>
        <country>England</country>
        <DOB>11 OCT 1937</DOB>
        <debut>6 OCT 1956</debut>
        <left>1 MAY 1973</left>
        <image>Bobby.jpg</image>
        <details>Sir Bobby Charlton is an English former footballer, regarded as one of the best midfielders of all time. Born in Northumberland England, Bobby had a lot of football players in his family. His elder brother was a keen footballer as a kid. Thus, Bobby too became fascinated with the game. However, he credits his grandmother and mother for pushing him to pursue profession football. He was studying in a grammer school in Bedlington when he was first spotted by Joe Armstrong, the chief scout for 'Manchester United'. He was taked in by 'Manchester United' at the age of 15. However, since he was from a middle class family, he also studied electrical engineering pursuing it as a backup career plan. In 1956, he made his club debut as part of the first team of 'Manchester United', and over the next few years, he secured a place for himself on the team. He ended up becoming the captain of the team in 1968 and led them to win the European Cup, the first for an English Premier League team. He had been the highest goal scorer for England and 'Manchester United' for many years. He represented the English national team in four FIFA World Cups since 1958.</details>
        <website>https://www.manutd.com/en/players-and-staff/detail/sir-bobby-charlton</website>
    </person>
    <person>
        <name>Paul Scholes</name>
        <position>Midfielder</position>
        <country>England</country>
        <DOB>16 Nov 1974</DOB>
        <debut>21 Sep 1994</debut>
        <left>19 May 2013</left>
        <image>Paul.jpg</image>
        <details>Paul Scholes is a well-known retired English footballer who played for Manchester United throughout his whole career. He played for the English National Football Team as well. One of the most decorated and successful footballers in history, he is currently a co-owner of Salford City Football Club and a television executive for BT Sport. Born in Salford, in Greater Manchester, he was a proficient cricketer as well as a footballer since his school days. After being spotted by a scout, he first got his opportunity to train with Manchester United at the age of 14. His professional career began in 1993. He played for the team for a total of nineteen years. He has represented the national team as well and took part in the 1998 and 2002 World Cups, as well as the UEFA Euro 2000 and Euro 2004. For his amazing skills, he is regarded as one of the best midfielders of his generation. Although he is asthmatic and suffers from Osgood-Schlatter disease, a knee condition, he managed to become one of the most proficient and popular international footballers, and won a total of 25 trophies in his career.  </details>
        <website>https://www.manutd.com/en/players-and-staff/detail/paul-scholes</website>
    </person>
    <person>
        <name>Gary Neville</name>
        <position>Defender</position>
        <country>England</country>
        <DOB>18 Feb 1975</DOB>
        <debut>17 Sep 1992</debut>
        <left>2 Feb 2011</left>
        <image>Gary.jpg</image>
        <details>Gary Neville is a former English footballer, born on 18th February 1975 in Bury, England. Neville was a right-back during his playing days but has also fulfilled the duties of a centre-back or a defensive midfielder when required. He preferred his right foot while playing the game. Neville was a part of the famed Class of 92 of Manchester United. Neville joined Manchester United in 1991. He captained the youth team to FA Youth Cup glory in his first season with the club. He was handed his debut by manager Sir Alex Ferguson in 1992. He was part of the youth revolution Sir Alex brought about at the club during the 1990s. Neville played his first game for the English national side in 1995. He made his debut under manager Terry Venables against Japan. He represented his nation in the 1998 and 2006 FIFA World Cups. Gary Neville has played for Manchester United FC throughout his career. He joined the team in 1991 and stayed at the club till 2011.</details>
        <website>https://www.manutd.com/en/players-and-staff/detail/gary-neville</website>
    </person>
    <person>
        <name>Dennis Viollet</name>
        <position>Forward</position>
        <country>England</country>
        <DOB>20 Sep 1933</DOB>
        <debut>10 Apr 1953</debut>
        <left>1 Jan 1962</left>
        <image>Dennis.jpg</image>
        <details>Dennis Sydney Viollet (20 September 1933 - 6 March 1999) was an English footballer who played for Manchester United and Stoke City as well as the England national team. He was famous as one of the Busby Babes and survived the Munich air disaster. After his retirement as player, he became a coach and spent most of his managerial career in the United States for various professional and school teams.</details>
        <website>https://www.manutd.com/en/players-and-staff/detail/dennis-viollet</website>
    </person>
    <person>
        <name>Wayne Rooney</name>
        <position>Forward</position>
        <country>England</country>
        <DOB>24 Oct 1985</DOB>
        <debut>28 Sep 2004</debut>
        <left>9 Jul 2017</left>
        <image>Wayney.jpg</image>
        <details>Wayne Rooney is a former English footballer widely regarded as England's best player. He is currently the manager of English League Championship club 'Derby County Football Club'. He was one of the world's most popular football players and has been named the 'England Player of the Year' four times. He scored 99 goals for a local junior league team at the age of nine which led to the Everton Football Club signing a contract with him. He made his professional debut with Everton in 2002 and within weeks became the youngest ever goal scorer in the history of premier league, a record which has now been surpassed. His career with Manchester United began in a great way, he scored an unforgettable hat trick against Fenerbahce in the Champions League. He played in the 2006, 2010, 2014 and 2018 World Cups for his national team. He helped Manchester United win four Premier League titles in five seasons.</details>
        <website>https://www.manutd.com/en/players-and-staff/detail/wayne-rooney</website>
    </person>
    <person>
        <name>Mark Hughes</name>
        <position>Forward</position>
        <country>Wales</country>
        <DOB>1 Nov 1963</DOB>
        <debut>30 Nov 1983</debut>
        <left>31 May 1995</left>
        <image>Mark.jpg</image>
        <details>Mark Hughes joined Manchester United as an Associate Schoolboy at 14 and became an apprentice in June 1980. He made his debut as a substitute in a 2-0 home win against Port Vale in the Milk Cup on 26th October 1983. Following a further substitute appearance in the European Cup Winners' Cup, Sparky made his first start, again in the Milk Cup, scoring in a 1-1 draw with Oxford United at the Manor Ground. He was named Player of the Year in 1991 and experienced glorious retribution with a man of the match display in the European Cup Winners' Cup final in Rotterdam, scoring twice in the 2-1 victory over old club Barcelona. It was while in Southampton that Hughes launched his managerial career, managing the Welsh National team on a part-time basis.</details>
        <website>https://www.manutd.com/en/players-and-staff/detail/mark-hughes</website>
    </person>
    <person>
        <name>Ruud Van Nistelrooy</name>
        <position>Forward</position>
        <country>Netherlands</country>
        <DOB>1 Jul 1976</DOB>
        <debut>12 Aug 2001</debut>
        <left>28 Jul 2006</left>
        <image>Ruud.jpg</image>
        <details>Ruud van Nistelrooy remains one of the game's most prolific goal scorers of all time. He enjoys the record of being the fourth highest goal scorer in UEFA Champions League history with a massive 56 goals. He was named the League's top scorer three times and was also the lead scorer in three different European domestic leagues. Despite these amazing results his name often disappears when discussing some of the greats, this is mainly due to his spats with fellow team players and a certain Sir Alex Ferguson. Currently he is the manager of the PSV youth team in Netherlands post retirement in 2012 at the age of 35. Both Nistelrooy and his wife are actively involved in the SOS Children's Villages.</details>
        <website>https://www.manutd.com/en/players-and-staff/detail/ruud-van-nistelrooy</website>
    </person>
    <person>
        <name>Cristiano Ronaldo</name>
        <position>Forward</position>
        <country>Portugal</country>
        <DOB>5 Feb 1985</DOB>
        <debut>16 Aug 2003</debut>
        <left>Current Player</left>
        <image>Cristiano.jpg</image>
        <details>Portuguese footballer Cristiano Ronaldo is often regarded as one of the best footballers to have ever played the game and his performances over the better part of a decade have only helped in reinforcing that belief among football fans. Ronaldo grew up in Madeira, Portugal but after graduating from the youth set up at Sporting CP he was immediately snapped up by English club Manchester United after his talent as a winger was spotted by their legendary manager Sir Alex Ferguson. Ronaldo spent six years at Manchester United and that was where he developed his game as a skillful, quick, lethal winger who could score goals and create opportunities for his team mates. He won plenty of trophies for Manchester United and also shone for the Portugual before he moved to Real Madrid as the world's most expensive player. At Real Madrid he has broken some of the most important goal scoring record that had stood for many years and also led the club to important trophies. Ronaldo is also the captain of the Portuguese national team and led them to victory in Euro 2016-their first ever triumph in a major tournament. He has also won plenty of individual awards that have further cemented his status as one of the world's premier footballers.</details>
        <website>https://www.manutd.com/en/players-and-staff/detail/cristiano-ronaldo</website>
    </person>
    <person>
        <name>Andy Cole</name>
        <position>Forward</position>
        <country>England</country>
        <DOB>15 Oct 1971</DOB>
        <debut>22 Jan 1995</debut>
        <left>29 Dec 2001</left>
        <image>Andy.jpg</image>
        <details>Andrew Alexander Cole is a former English professional footballer who played as a forward. Cole was one of the greatest strikers in Premier League history, but, as Ian Wright, he was never able to take his skills to the international stage. In 2000, The Cole Formerly Known As Andy revealed that he wanted to be known as Andrew Cole, following in the footsteps of The Artist Formerly Known As Prince. His work with Manchester United is well-known, as the club paid a British record transfer fee to sign him away from Newcastle United. He won eight major trophies during his six years at Manchester United, including the Premier League Treble, FA Cup, and UEFA Champions League in 1999.</details>
        <website>https://www.manutd.com/en/players-and-staff/detail/andy-cole</website>
    </person>
    <person>
        <name>Bryan Robson</name>
        <position>Midfielder</position>
        <country>England</country>
        <DOB>11 Jan 1957</DOB>
        <debut>7 Oct 1981</debut>
        <left>31 May 1994</left>
        <image>Bryan.jpg</image>
        <details>Manchester United has a rich legacy of players who have made a mark at the club to make it arguably the most successful club in the British Isles. While it has ruled the English football for a quarter of a century now, its incredible foundation can be attributed to their mercurial and legendary captain Bryan Robson OBE. He is a retired midfielder who was played notably for the Red Devils and West Brom and for English national team. He scored 40 goals in close to 200 league games before joining Manchester United in 1981, making him the record signing of that time. After retirement, Robson has taken up management. It has been a mixed bag for "Robbo" which include a disappointing but ultimately face saving spell at boyhood club West Ham. He has also coached the Thailand national football team.</details>
        <website>https://www.manutd.com/en/players-and-staff/detail/bryan-robson</website>
    </person>
    <person>
        <name>David Beckham</name>
        <position>Midfielder</position>
        <country>England</country>
        <DOB>2 May 1975</DOB>
        <debut>23 Sep 1992</debut>
        <left>2 Jul 2003</left>
        <image>David.jpg</image>
        <details>David Robert Joseph Beckham is a former English professional football player. During his playing days, he became one of the most famous footballers in the world owing to his successful stints at some of the most famous clubs and also for his skills as a midfielder that elevated him above many of his contemporaries. Beckham started off as a footballer in his home town of London and played for some local clubs before he entered the training scheme for young players at Manchester United. At Manchester United, David Beckham tasted success as the club went on an unprecedented winning spree through the mid and late 1990s. He won the coveted 'treble' with Manchester United and became one of their most famous players before going on to play for Real Madrid, AC Milan, Paris Saint-Germain and Major League Soccer team LA Galaxy in the United States. David Beckham was also an integral part of the supposed 'Golden Generation' of England national football team and captained the team for a major part of his career; however the team did not taste the success that was expected of it. Beckham has also been one of the biggest faces in the endorsement industry and has consistently been ranked among the richest footballers in the world throughout his career.</details>
        <website>https://www.manutd.com/en/players-and-staff/detail/david-beckham</website>
    </person>
</people>




